[  
{
    "question": "Which district has the lowest population in Nepal?",
    "option1": "Manang",
    "option2": "Mustang",
    "option3": "Dolpa",
    "option4": "Humla",
    "correctAns": "option1",
    "level": "2"
},
{
    "question": "What is the oldest newspaper of Nepal?",
    "option1": "Gorkhapatra",
    "option2": "Kantipur",
    "option3": "The Rising Nepal",
    "option4": "Nagarik",
    "correctAns": "option1",
    "level": "2"
},
{
    "question": "Who is the first Nepali to climb Mount Everest without oxygen?",
    "option1": "Pasang Lhamu Sherpa",
    "option2": "Phurba Tenzing Sherpa",
    "option3": "Aang Rita Sherpa",
    "option4": "Lhakpa Sherpa",
    "correctAns": "option3",
    "level": "3"
},
    {
        "question": "Which river flows towards north in Nepal?",
        "option1": "Karnali",
        "option2": "Koshi",
        "option3": "Narayani",
        "option4": "Gandaki",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "2"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "In which district is Chamero Gupha (bat's cave) situated?",
        "option1": "Kaski",
        "option2": "Dang",
        "option3": "Rolpa",
        "option4": "Pyuthan",
        "correctAns": "option2",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which district is Tilicho Lake located?",
        "option1": "Mustang",
        "option2": "Manang",
        "option3": "Dolpa",
        "option4": "Solukhumbu",
        "correctAns": "option2",
        "level": "2"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Which is the deepest lake of Nepal?",
        "option1": "Phoksundo Lake",
        "option2": "Rara Lake",
        "option3": "Tilicho Lake",
        "option4": "Shey Phoksundo Lake",
        "correctAns": "option4",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the singer of 'Lakhau Hajarau'?",
        "option1": "Yabesh Thapa",
        "option2": "Samir Shrestha",
        "option3": "Shashwot Khadka",
        "option4": "bekcha",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Nepali band sang 'Bagaicha'?",
        "option1": "1974 AD",
        "option2": "Nepathya",
        "option3": "Kta haru",
        "option4": "Phosphenes",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which song is this from: 'Kalo lamo pareli kesha'?",
        "option1": "Malai nasodha",
        "option2": "Gajalu ti thula thula aakha",
        "option3": "Tutnu Thiyo Tutyo Mutu",
        "option4": "Kehi Mitho Baat Gara",
        "correctAns": "option2",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first rapper of Nepal?",
        "option1": "Uniq Poet",
        "option2": "Yama Buddha",
        "option3": "Girish Khatiwada",
        "option4": "Laure",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the singer for 'Aaudai Jadai'?",
        "option1": "The Uglyz",
        "option2": "Kush",
        "option3": "1974 AD",
        "option4": "Ulto Pulto",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most viewed Nepali song in YouTube?",
        "option1": "Saali Man Paryo",
        "option2": "Phul Butte Sari",
        "option3": "Gojima Daam Chaina",
        "option4": "Kutu ma kutu",
        "correctAns": "option4",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the most viewed song of Bipul Chhetri on Spotify?",
        "option1": "Asaar",
        "option2": "Syndicate",
        "option3": "Wildfire",
        "option4": "Ram sailee",
        "correctAns": "option4",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the singer of 'Mohani lagla hai'?",
        "option1": "Narayan Gopal",
        "option2": "Bartika Eam Rai",
        "option3": "Nattu Shah",
        "option4": "Sajjan Raj Vaidya",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "2"
    }
]
